I've got an order of the beggars, give me my council, the council, the council, for two days, on the fifth, 20.5.
But the impotence, give them personal appearances, none, 30, plenty of lists.
Oh, show proof.
Say it.
He's deaf.
Hi.
Jones, hi.
On the side, Parker.
Hi.
Four minutes from the July 15th and then July 22nd, the beggars, give them meetings.
Second.
Hi.
He's deaf.
Jones, hi.
On the side, Parker.
Hi.
Five.
Grand agreement with the US Department of Transportation, we're fiscal year 24.
Safe streets and roads.
We're all grant program.
For future implementation of safety improvements to the existing infrastructure.
Linda.
This basically is the, uh, to the green at the end.
President, Mr. Butler.
Do we still have to prove it?
It says action.
I'll explain it.
I'll make motion.
Jones, hi.
Barnes, hi.
He's dead.
Hi.
Linda.
Parker.
Six.
Discussion and action.
I'm request for approval for the Mymer Route 6616.
Linda.
Chondom.
I'm just like a buffer.
I think they can do it.
They can do it.
the Christmas one the balls something with that I mean that's kind of our
thing other than that I like the rest of them just the Christmas one
star at the number of 66 but might have not passed it there's the ball that you are here
remember did say you are here was the big word change that this is kind of what I
like on a wall because that's our goal to go all into changes that I did I think
that Christmas ball we're going to do other murals I know Kelly's not here in the
life that we're on the arts and you made it to where you would have actually
the silver or the her that's awesome
the flag is
everybody like this what everybody will be on and I really do that and this one
we're talking about as the name of American language and how I would set up
them but it's more tribal and that we were going to talk about this with your ears
artists perhaps to do that one.
Very collaboration.
You know, these use students to help them out.
That's the thing.
That is pricing for this.
I've been on the Arts and Humanity Council for a girl.
I think it's called 50.
And then 10 to give the changeups.
That's very reasonable.
So we're talking about the 1,500 total.
4.
Yeah.
But I didn't know what it was.
But now we talked about 4 changes.
10 changes.
If you want more changes.
7.
We're going to need that.
So that is good.
2.
10.
Have a quick question.
On the participates for the how likely have people to stop and all those numbers.
And you're the how many participants are there?
How many participants are there?
Okay.
I guess I'm the first.
I like the block better.
Except for the A.
The A looks weird to me.
That was actually still wrong.
I'm like, you know, that to me is hard to see that.
And the A is just looks weird.
It looks out of place with the only block better.
I don't know that.
Probably something you can fix easy.
But I love this one.
I love that one.
We'll run.
Love that one.
That one.
I think we can.
Yeah.
I think getting that deal with Christmas balls or something.
We may be a little better because that's kind of, you know,
a lot of our Christmas of balls around the Christmas balls.
This is only my second Christmas.
All right.
We could make something like...
I think we do something really cool.
People may stop buying.
I think we can get here too.
Or even if even if we did like the.
It's a story.
My I'm a downtown Christmas with the old darling hanging across with the ball.
It's a picture with the free set.
So that may be a.
A cooler picture for the Christmas.
But oh, that.
All right.
It looks pretty good.
Let's see.
It's funny.
Like on certain ones.
I like the.
The font.
With certain ones.
Like the one with the triangle.
Well.
I like the bolder font.
So it's like the card.
I like the person.
Is the font staying?
Well.
Is the font like the front of the piece when we do around it?
I think she's right though.
The pin on the picture.
Look how the font does it better.
Yeah.
There's a.
Pass around.
There's right here.
I can't have a one for the person, just personal one, but like that one, yeah, but just doing that.
On this one, the cursing, the cursing, yes.
No, not that one, but that one, she, I do like that one better.
It comes down, too.
Isn't it weird to have a personality?
There's a finder.
I know.
That's right.
It comes down, too.
It's a day, but I'm more interested.
First, then, by one day.
On the other hand.
It, it, for some day.
That's right.
Does that look good?
Yeah, I like the cursing better myself.
Usually.
I like it.
I like the cursing.
They say they're ready for all the tips.
Or am I, am I a problem?
What should I say?
It's fine for the word.
I think they're, I think they're, I don't know how to do this.
That's fine.
That's fine for my favourite one.
And it gets me way better.
And I think we leave it.
If you look at the word Miami too much, it looks weird.
It starts not looking like it should spell something.
Like our regional chamber of commerce.
It's kind of got that cursive look to it as well.
So it almost feels like we stick with that motif.
It's not necessarily the same form.
We have some kind of standardization.
We have to reservation.
So what do I think of the other picture?
I like them.
I hate them like this one.
This reminds me of our Christmas.
Like vintage hallmarking.
Christmas.
I know that the balls are like that.
You got to do the balls.
Got to do the balls.
I'm just like it.
That's not my way.
Great.
Yeah.
There's a teacher.
I think you have the biggest ball that we're discussing, yeah, I'll tell you about that.
Oh, I've got the picture right here. I'll send it to you. I've got the picture right here.
So, we're all in agreement with all the cars of, yes.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, so we're all in agreement with all the cars of stuff. That was a nice thing, probably.
Okay.
I like the ball.
Yeah.
On the tribal one, I think you've got to keep that one as simple as possible.
The problem, and we were talking about it up here, you'll please six and make three mad.
So, I think the more vanilla you can keep that one, if it's just...
Mm-hmm.
They'll still not agree, but I think the more vanilla they'll be better.
That's perfect.
Oh, yeah.
I want to get that for a tattoo.
Oh.
I wish we should all get a tattoo.
Yeah.
We go one after the other.
We can make a tattoo.
Yeah.
I have a quick question about the tribal one.
Are you going to include all of the tribal...
No, I don't.
Okay.
Okay. Yeah.
All of all.
Okay.
It's just pronounced differently.
I would still suggest taking that tattoo, see, and make sure that he gets the thumbs up from there.
Yeah, we are like that.
That should be coming up pretty quickly.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't think that's not what they've been cared about the rest.
What I'm saying.
What I'm saying is that they've been cared about.
That's what it's saying.
It's what it's saying.
What do you need?
You both have it in your budget.
Both have it in your budget.
They handle it.
As long as they don't go over 20,000, we don't have to do it.
That was such a good move. Who did I deal with? I'll make motion to approve with some of the changes that we
Second hi
I
Seven mirrors on nation to point mark me down to the minus senior center advisory board and the minus senior center incorporated board of director
Motion to approve take
Hey another new business if any for the rhythm suppose to listen to nine staff or 10 mayor and counsel from your native now
But I just want to have that there's going on this week
So if you guys have a free night or anything and like we'd like to go support the kid
Is out there. They've been working really hard and then this month's also a real
I really appreciate the words that we're spoken at our grand opening ceremony for the new airport terminal
This was a big decision for us. It was a gutsy call. I think it's going to pay off in the long run
I know we'll have our naysayers
But I was happy to see some of our naysayers there supporting us
So that's good to see that some of those people that were once kind against us are starting to see our vision and see
What what what are goals are and what we kind of are trying to accomplish here. I mean we're all always going to have the
People who aren't happy with whatever and that's okay because we should use that to drive us to just be better
So
But it was neat it was cool to hear the from an outside perspective here people talk about what it was which which was it was a it was a risk and
And I think it was a great payoff. Well, I think we'll continue to see dividends so hats off to all of us for
Being willing to think outside the box. I want to kind of go on that to appreciate it also
Also, I want to say our Route 66 mess this year was great. It was awesome out there this year
Trendy you've done a fantastic job and you put in a lot of hard work in a lot of hours plus our city guys
There are all of you Kevin the street guys. You guys did an awesome job. I mean Main Street was picked back up early on Sunday morning
It didn't even look like there was really anything
All-all Main Street you got a fabulous job. We got a great city
So thank you all for everything you all day. That was down there almost 730 running and
Great job
make it easy for us to make these both decisions and you make it easy for us to bet on ourselves
and that's because they have great employees here to get the job done.
And he got pulled together.
Moll is the way it's odd.
We have HR down there, clean the building for the airport.
And no matter what we decide to be here, you guys make it happen.
You know, we make the decisions and say this is the direction we're going.
And you guys are the state staff.
Get in there and get the hard work done.
So, you make us look good by the work you guys do.
So, we'd greatly appreciate all of you, all your staff.
I know a lot of your staff don't hear from us, but please pass on.
We appreciate all of our hard work.
Try to let Kevin said, good as to you.
Your first year to do it for the 66 festival and it's our best one.
In my opinion, it's our best one, but far.
I know you and your team put in a lot of hard work.
And probably there's some sleepless nights to pull it off, but I only had one negative comment.
The whole time.
And it was fixed.
So, I just appreciate everybody in this city because employees here do great work.
And I know you guys don't always hear the pause this, but I think that's changing too.
I think people in this community are starting to notice that it's not as bad as what they think it is here.
And that's, again, because of all of you and what you guys do.
So, keep making us look, we appreciate it.
I like to point out I want to quit a job because I have to listen.
No quit, Molly.
No, don't.
If you want to, if you love it, you pose cool place.
If you want to.
If you pose.
Say you might as a communications.
The only thing I have that you have touched on is tonight is the National Night Out.
And the splash pad.
It is going on right now from 530 to 830.
So, if you get a chance, go to the splash pad and meet the emergency services that are there.
Please fire, EMTs, dispatch, food trucks.
There's all kinds of stuff going on out there.
Yeah.
It isn't meeting.
She's so.
I think if you feel a long way to support our first responders.
Definitely see a show in that evening of just for a few minutes.
I know we all got families.
I think we could stop by for a few minutes.
Just let them know we support them.
It means a lot to them.
Maybe not ever.
Yeah.
It's a meeting.
Molly posted the public.
I've been noticing.
I know when I.
I drove by there before I came here and it was already pretty cool.
I mean, they were out there.
If you'd trucks would go in and they're splash pad was full.
The.
Well, chronic areas packed.
So.
We extended the timer.
She's so little run light.
I need to go.
I'm sorry.
12.
Gentlemen.
Motion.
Second.
Hi.
All right.